Huth, Geoffrey A.; Papers mss137
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- pdqb Records, 1989-2006; 5; 1.25 cubic ft.
  - pdqb Layouts to Publications, 1989; 1991-1992; 1999-2006; 5.2; 0.4 cubic ft.
    - pdqb #21: GNET Huth, "Wishing Perfect! Holidays", eXmaSscard #7, 5 December 1993 (Box 1 (5-pdqb Records), Folder 8)
    - pdqb #23: GNET Huth, "star light night dream dance sleep drift", 22 November 1994 (Box 1 (5-pdqb Records), Folder 9)
    - pdqb #28: Around Erin's Town #4, 2 August 1996 (Box 1 (5-pdqb Records), Folder 10)
    - pdqb #64: Geof Huth, Les cartouches de le reve, 8 February 2004 (Box 1 (5-pdqb Records), Folder 11)
    - pdqb #79: Geof Huth, "Household Words" The Words You Use Only at Home, and Why, 17 October 1998 (Box 1 (5-pdqb Records), Folder 12)
    - pdqb #80: GNET Huth, star, eXmaSscard #12, 13 December 1998 (Box 1 (5-pdqb Records), Folder 13)
    - pdqb #83: GNET Huth, "A Few Scenes from the past year...", eXmaSscard #14, 18 December 2000 (Box 1 (5-pdqb Records), Folder 14)
    - pdqb #84: Huth, Geof, "Waking Up at Home", 10 October 1995 (Box 1 (5-pdqb Records), Folder 15)
    - pdqb #85: ebbtide floodtide riptide, eXmaSscard #15, 15 December 2001 (Box 1 (5-pdqb Records), Folder 16)
    - pdqb #86: geof Huth/ pdqb/anarchivist, 18 May 2002 (Box 1 (5-pdqb Records), Folder 17)
    - pdqb #87: erin huth, Graduation Party Invitation, 25 May 2002 (Box 1 (5-pdqb Records), Folder 18)
    - pdqb #88: Pumpkin Day 2002, 26 October 2002 (Box 1 (5-pdqb Records), Folder 19)
    - pdqb #90: "smooth", eXmaSscard #16, 13 December 2002 (Box 1 (5-pdqb Records), Folder 20)
    - pdqb #92: Film Clips #4, 31 December 2002 (Box 1 (5-pdqb Records), Folder 21)
    - pdqb #94: Mango Day 2003, 22 June 2003 (Box 1 (5-pdqb Records), Folder 22)
    - pdqb #95: Huth, Geof, Records as Memory: Caring for and Using Family Records, 1 November 2003 (Box 1 (5-pdqb Records), Folder 23)
    - pdqb #96: Huth, Geof: Preparing for a Research Trip, 1 November 2003 (Box 1 (5-pdqb Records), Folder 24)
    - pdqb #97: Pumpkin Day 2003, 25 October 2003 (Box 1 (5-pdqb Records), Folder 25)
    - pdqb #98: Greetings from the Snowglobe, 17 December 2003 (Box 1 (5-pdqb Records), Folder 26)
    - pdqb #100: Mango Day 2004, 10 July 2004 (Box 1 (5-pdqb Records), Folder 27)
    - pdqb #102: Pumpkin Day 2004, 24 October 2004 (Box 1 (5-pdqb Records), Folder 28)
    - pdqb #103: "the idea of snow", eXmaSscard #18, 19 December 2004 (Box 1 (5-pdqb Records), Folder 29)
    - pdqb #104: Sweet Potato Day 2005, 9 January 2005 (Box 1 (5-pdqb Records), Folder 30)
    - pdqb #105: Geof Huth, Realfabetizations, 8 February 2005 (Box 1 (5-pdqb Records), Folder 31)
    - pdqb #106: Carrot Day 2005, 21 May 2005 (Box 1 (5-pdqb Records), Folder 32)
    - pdqb #107: Geof Huth, "foureff", 16 July 2005 (Box 1 (5-pdqb Records), Folder 33)
    - pdqb #109: Geof Huth, "fourteefive", Something like a reading for Jawbone in Albany, New York, 2005 September 23 (Box 1 (5-pdqb Records), Folder 34)
    - pdqb #110: Pumpkin Day 2005, 9 October 2005 (Box 1 (5-pdqb Records), Folder 35)
    - pdqb #111: Geof Huth, "wesleep", 17 December 2005 (Box 1 (5-pdqb Records), Folder 36)
    - pdqb #113: Geof Huth, "fiddlehuth #1", 28 July 2006 (Box 1 (5-pdqb Records), Folder 37)
  - Administrative Records, 1990-1991; 2006; 5.3; 0.1 cubic ft.
    Includes printed reviews of pdqb publications and lists of people receiving some pdqb publications.
    Arranged alphabetically by folder title.
    - pdqb List, 2006 (Box 1 (5-pdqb Records), Folder 1)
    - Recipients of pdqb Publications, 1990-1991 (Box 1 (5-pdqb Records), Folder 2)
    - Reviews of pdqb, 1991 (Box 1 (5-pdqb Records), Folder 3)
  - Oversized Items, 5.4
    - pdqb #13, New York State Archives and Records Administration, 7 June 1992 (Box 1 (5-pdqb Records), Folder 1)
    - pdqb Layouts, pdqb #101: The Murphybed Huthache, 21 October 2004 (Box 1 (5-pdqb Records), Folder 2)
    - 2 film containers, G. Huth, 85 for Killer Whale, pdqb #5, 12 November 1990 (Box 1 (5-pdqb Records))
    - Black box, Film Clips #3, Undated (Box 1 (5-pdqb Records))
- qbdp Records, 1991-1992; 2002; 2004-2006; 6; 0.75 cubic ft.
  The micropress qbdp releases only tiny runs of mailart. The series includes single copies of the mailart produced by Geof Huth in the qbdp series and occasional copies of layouts for same. The micropress qbdp was officially initiated in May 2004, when Huth began to produce mailart in small editions, saving one copy of each for his files. The original issues of Film Clips, the mailart zine originally released by pdqb were retronumbered as the first numbers of qbdp, and issues from Film Clips are now released only under the qbdp imprint.
  - qbdp Publications, 1991-1992; 2002; 2004-2006; 6.1; 0.5 cubic ft.
    Includes one copy of every qbdp mailart item ever released.
    Arranged numerically by qbdp number, which coincides with chronological order with the exception of qbdp # 101.
    - qbdp #1, retronumbered, Film Clips #1, A Self-Destructing Compilation of Cultural Iconography and Mail Art or Life for the Autodidact, 19 February 1991 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 1)
    - qbdp #2, retronumbered, Film Clips #2, A Self-Destructing Compilation of Cultural Iconography and Mail Art or The Iconoclast's Amanuensis Incognito, 21 September 1991 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 2)
    - qbdp #3, retronumbered, Film Clips #3, A Self-Destructing Compilation of Cultural Iconography and Mail Art or The Adept's Idioticon Conflablated, 27 October 1992 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 3)
    - qbdp #4, retronumbered, Film Clips #4, A Self-Destructing Compilation of Cultural Iconography and Mail Art or The Illeist's Frame of Reference Entombed, 31 December 2002 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 4)
    - qbdp #5, Inscriptions on Birch Bark, 17 May 2004 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 5)
    - qbdp #6, New Improved American Flag, 22 May 2004 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 6)
    - qbdp #7, metyou, 26 May 2004 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 7)
    - qbdp #8, cross wayss, 29 May 2004 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 8)
    - qbdp #9, AfHtJI, 14 June 2004 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 9)
    - qbdp #10, moonn, 19 June 2004 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 10)
    - qbdp #11, SYSTemIa, 26 June 2004 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 11)
    - qbdp #12, tripl3ts, 2 July 2004 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 12)
    - qbdp #13, PRESENCES, 3 July 2004 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 13)
    - qbdp #14, V+S+BL+GHT, 4 July 2004 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 14)
    - qbdp #15, lakeeast, 10 July 2004 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 15)
    - qbdp #16, electric garden, 24 July 2004 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 16)
    - qbdp #17, gnail 1 finjer 1 thumn, 1 August 2004 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 17)
    - qbdp #18, a s w Y a, 6 August 2004 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 18)
    - qbdp #19, A slit beside, 8 August 2004 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 19)
    - qbdp #20, the Letter A, 15 August 2004 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 20)
    - qbdp #21, rhjly, 19 August 2004 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 21)
    - qbdp #22, Loonless Pond, 20 August 2004 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 22)
    - qbdp #23, Camping by Pharaoh Mountain, 22 August 2004 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 23)
    - qbdp #24, First 1/2 VJ S TT Fist, 29 August 2004 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 24)
    - qbdp #25, sp pr rt th ha, 5 September 2004 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 25)
    - qbdp #26, HEM+HAW, 6 September 2004 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 26)
    - qbdp #27, mn/wv, 12 September 2004 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 27)
    - qbdp #28, FATE, 22 September 2004 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 28)
    - qbdp #29, Cartouche, 25 September 2004 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 29)
    - qbdp #30, seIze, 26 September 2004 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 30)
    - qbdp #31, wordwinds, 30 September 2004 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 31)
    - qbdp #32, (eyg)(eau)(auo)(Eft), 1 October 2004 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 32)
    - qbdp #33, "SKREED", 2 October 2004 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 33)
    - qbdp #34, Danauzgy, 10 October 2004 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 34)
    - qbdp #35, MY NAME IS, 11 October 2004 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 35)
    - qbdp #36, CLUNAR ELLIPSE, 27 October 2004 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 36)
    - qbdp #37, the all-seeing eye becomes, 9 November 2004 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 37)
    - qbdp #38, DAY SeE, IOH IOI, 2004 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 38)
    - qbdp #39, nuung being, 9 December 2004 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 39)
    - qbdp #40, EYE, 9 December 2004 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 40)
    - qbdp #41, ON THIS SITE since 31 December 2004, Undated (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 41)
    - qbdp #42, quincelt, 16 January 2005 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 42)
    - qbdp #43, fLoor, 11 February 2005 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 43)
    - qbdp #44, Ever now a thought, 20 February 2005 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 44)
    - qbdp #45, ObJecT Scrapmail #1, 21 February 2005 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 45)
    - qbdp #46, Scrapmail #1, 31 March 2005 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 46)
    - qbdp #47, read, 1 April 2005 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 47)
    - qbdp #48, all of it now, 6 April 2005 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 48)
    - qbdp #49, A OMN e, 8 April 2005 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 49)
    - qbdp #50, ExElEncE, 11 April 2005 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 50)
    - qbdp #51, hubrise, 26 April 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 1)
    - qbdp #52, starnight, 27 April 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 2)
    - qbdp #53, uimmy faces, 28 April 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 3)
    - qbdp #54, ovo, 11 May 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 4)
    - qbdp #55, leafves of foleads, 12 May 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 5)
    - qbdp #56, A Selection from the Museum of Modern Writing, 18 May 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 6)
    - qbdp #57, Rt, 28 May 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 7)
    - qbdp #58, The monogram of Titus the Great, 29 May 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 8)
    - qbdp #59, The Inevitable Course of Water, 30 May 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 9)
    - qbdp #60, His Holiness of Rags, 8 June 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 10)
    - qbdp #61, oh my/flagging, 9 June 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 11)
    - qbdp #62, (k/p/[f/r])/ee[zip]ing, 10 June 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 12)
    - qbdp #63, 23 Heust, 11 June 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 13)
    - qbdp #64, The Face of Typr, 12 June 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 14)
    - qbdp #65, Sssssssea, 13 June 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 15)
    - qbdp #66, zephyr/ari3, 15 June 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 16)
    - qbdp #67, writ/wrat/wrot, 21 June 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 17)
    - qbdp #68, Digraphs and Trigraphs, 25 June 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 18)
    - qbdp #69, VRR, 26 June 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 19)
    - qbdp #70, self seen, 27 June 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 20)
    - qbdp #71, The 3 States of Nothingness, 2 July 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 21)
    - qbdp #72, sigh, 3 July 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 22)
    - qbdp #73, live, 4 July 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 23)
    - qbdp #74, darkless, 17 July 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 24)
    - qbdp #75, "My tremor", 18 July 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 25)
    - qbdp #76, slit, 19 July 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 26)
    - qbdp #77, SKRUVE, 24 July 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 27)
    - qbdp #78, SLack, 26 July 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 28)
    - qbdp #79, S/I/wright, 6 August 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 29)
    - qbdp #80, The Character Symbolizing "to Be", 7 August 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 30)
    - qbdp #81, HH&s, 12 August 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 31)
    - qbdp #82, aRroW, 13 August 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 32)
    - qbdp #83, message, 14 August 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 33)
    - qbdp #84, afRodITes, Homage to Bill Keith, 15 August 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 34)
    - qbdp #85, psilence, 16 August 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 35)
    - qbdp #86, [tide], 17 August 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 36)
    - qbdp #87, misnumbered 86, mn/mn, 18 August 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 37)
    - qbdp #88, misnumbered 87, iiiiiiiiris, 19 August 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 38)
    - qbdp #89, misnumbered 88, The Dream of K., 20 August 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 39)
    - qbdp #90, misnumbered 89, A OMN e, 22 August 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 40)
    - qbdp #91, misnumbered 90, 2 1/2 Aitches, 23 August 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 41)
    - qbdp #92, The Correction of the Alphabet, 27 August 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 42)
    - qbdp #93, secret, 2 September 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 43)
    - qbdp #94, The City of New Orleans, August 29, 2005, 3 September 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 44)
    - qbdp #95, 2 Cuts, 5 September 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 45)
    - qbdp #96, unnumbered original, 12534sss, 16 September 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 46)
    - qbdp #97, The Way Our Words Transform in Flight, 22 September 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 47)
    - qbdp #98, ess/em, 27 September 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 48)
    - qbdp #99, reseen, 21 October 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 49)
    - qbdp #100, EARMARK, 22 October 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 50)
    - qbdp #101, Not Created Yet, folder is empty, Undated (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 51)
    - qbdp #102, The Wind's Flames, 27 October 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 52)
    - qbdp #103, page, 2 November 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 53)
    - qbdp #104, The map of my alphabet, 15 November 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 54)
    - qbdp #105, WORD page snds AURA, 24 November 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 55)
    - qbdp #106, Felt, iflfElTiT+ieNclRcled1, 25 November 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 56)
    - qbdp #107, &I.e.G., 26 November 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 57)
    - qbdp #108, ONE flake OVER, 9 December 2005 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 58)
    - qbdp #109, chaos/dugoz, 4 September 2006 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 59)
    - qbdp #110, if A fire, 8 September 2006 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 60)
    - qbdp #111, issue abcess, 10 September 2006 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 61)
    - qbdp #112, sail/awave, 21 September 2006 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 62)
    - qbdp #113, nk, 10 October 2006 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 63)
    - qbdp #114, quail, 13 October 2006 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 64)
    - qbdp #115, S23N, 23 October 2006 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 65)
    - qbdp #116, arcHI'vE, 26 October 2006 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 66)
    - qbdp #117, S(ó)ent, 27 October 2006 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 67)
    - qbdp #118, S/&, 5 November 2006 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 68)
    - qbdp #119, Dear ........, 28 November 2006 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 69)
    - qbdp #120, Voici l'oiseau dans l'arbre, 29 November 2006 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 70)
    - qbdp #121, airlIGht, 30 November 2006 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 71)
    - qbdp #122, wes, 11 December 2006 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 72)
    - qbdp #123, coUnt, 14 December 2006 (Box 2 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 73)
  - qbdp Layouts to Publications, 2004-2006; 6.2; 0.25 cubic ft.
    Includes layout copies of many qbdp publications.
    - qbdp #6: New Improved American Flag, 22 May 2004 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 1)
    - qbdp #29: Cartouche, 25 September 2004 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 2)
    - qbdp #36: CLUNAR ELLIPSE, 27 October 2004 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 3)
    - qbdp #41: ON THIS SITE, 31 December 2004 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 4)
    - qbdp #41: ON THIS SITE, 31 December 2004 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 5)
    - qbdp #68: Digraphs and Trigraphs, 25 July 2005 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 6)
    - qbdp #77: SKRUVE, 24 July 2005 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 7)
    - qbdp #79: S/1/wright, 6 August 2005 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 8)
    - qbdp #94: The City of New Orleans, August 29, 2005, 3 September 2005 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 9)
    - qbdp #107: &I.e.G., 26 November 2005 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 10)
    - qbdp #114: quail, 13 October 2006 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 11)
    - qbdp #116: arcHIiVE, 26 October 2006 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 12)
    - qbdp #119: Dear ........, 28 November 2006 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 13)
    - qbdp #120: Voici l'oiseau dans l'arbre, 29 November 2006 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 14)
    - qbdp #121: airlIGht, 30 November 2006 (Box 1 (6-qbdp Records), Folder 15)
- CWM Records, 1989-1993; 7; 0.25 cubic ft.
  This series consists of the records of the art and literary magazine CWM co-edited with David C. Kopaska-Merkel, including announcements, correspondence, and two copies of issue # 1.
  - Announcements, 1989-1992 (Box 1 (7-CWM Records), Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1990-1993 (Box 1 (7-CWM Records), Folder 2)
  - CWM #1, 1992 (Box 1 (7-CWM Records), Folder 3)
  - CWM #1 Layouts, 1992 (Box 1 (7-CWM Records), Folder 4)
  - Guidelines, 1992 (Box 1 (7-CWM Records), Folder 5)
  - Official Logo, 1990 (Box 1 (7-CWM Records), Folder 6)
  - Photographs, 1992 (Box 1 (7-CWM Records), Folder 7)
  - Rejection Letter, 1992 (Box 1 (7-CWM Records), Folder 8)
  - Reviews, 1993 (Box 1 (7-CWM Records), Folder 9)
  - Submitted Logos, 1990 (Box 1 (7-CWM Records), Folder 10)
  - Themes for Issues, 1992 (Box 1 (7-CWM Records), Folder 11)
- Weblogs, 2003-2006; 8; 1.25 cubic ft. + 1.5 GB
  Starting at the end of 2003, much of Geof Huth's artistic output was focused on his work on weblogs. This series consists of paper and electronic copies of the various weblogs produced by Huth, one of which is a joint blog with D. Ross Priddle. This series includes blog files (archived copies of each blog), electronic files (copies of the electronic files used to created the blogs), and paper files (printouts of the weblogs).
  - Subseries A: Alongside a Gibbous Orange Moon, 2004; 1 folder + unknown MB
    Consists of archived electronic copies and paper copies of the weblog Alongside a Gibbous Orange Moon, which documents the Huth family's April 2004 trip to Florida's Gulf Coast. The URL for the weblog refers to the family's shorthand for itself: "GNET" stands for "Geof, Nancy, Erin, and Tim". URL: http://gnethuth.blogspot.com
    Blog Files: Arranged in reverse chronological order. Consists of an archived copy of the weblog.
    Paper Files: Arranged in chronological order of blog posting. Consists of a printout the weblog.
  - Subseries B: The Anarchivist, 2006 January-2006 August; 1 folder + unknown MB (Box 1 (8-Weblogs), Folder 1)
    Consists of an occasional weblog that discusses archival issues. Includes reprints of and original articles written by Geof Huth and documentation of some of the professional conferences he attended. URL: http://anarchivist.blogspot.com; Blog Files: Arranged in reverse chronological order. Consists of an archived copy of the weblog.; Paper Files: Arranged in chronological order by month and thereunder in reverse chronological order of blog posting. Consists of a printout the weblog.
  - Subseries C: bqpd: the bookworks, 1999-2005; 1 folder + unknown MB (Box 1 (8-Weblogs), Folder 2)
    This weblog documents and describes the unique books (journals, bookworks, and notebooks) produced by Geof Huth. Some entries are retrodated so the postings coincide with the original date of publication of the books. URL: http://bqpd.blogspot.com; Blog Files: Arranged in reverse chronological order. Consists of an archived copy of the weblog.; Paper Files: Arranged in chronological order by month and thereunder in reverse chronological order of blog posting. Consists of a printout the weblog.
  - Subseries D: dbpq, 2005; 1 folder + unknown MB
    A joint weblog produced with D. Ross Priddle that includes documentation of the micropress dbqp. URL: http://dbpq.blogspot.com
    Paper Files: Arranged in chronological order by month and thereunder in reverse chronological order of blog posting. Consists of a printout the weblog.
  - Subseries E: dbqp: visualizing poetics, 2003-2006; 1 cubic feet + unknown MB
    Geof Huth's primary weblog, dbqp: visualizing poetics focuses on discussions of visual poetry and other forms of verbo-visual expression. The weblog's prospectus describes the blog as "A kaleidoscopic review of visual poetry and related forms of art over the centuries, joined with the recollections of one contemporary visual poet. Topics of interest include visual prose, comics art, illustrated books, minimalist poetry, and visually-enhanced textual poetry". This weblog usually includes one posting per day. URL: http://dbqp.blogspot.com
    Electronic Files: Includes drafts of blog entries, copies of images used on the blog, and periodic captures of the blog template. Consists of 963 MB of files.
  - Subseries F: dbqplist, 2003-2004; 1 folder + unknown MB (Box 1 (8-Weblogs), Folder 3)
    This weblog documents and describes the publications released by dbqp. Some entries are retrodated so the postings coincide with or appear close to the original date of publication of the issues. URL: http://dbqplist.blogspot.com; Blog Files: Arranged in reverse chronological order. Consists of an archived copy of the weblog.; Paper Files: Arranged in chronological order by month and thereunder in reverse chronological order of blog posting. Consists of a printout the weblog.
  - Subseries G: Geof Huth, 2006; 1 folder + unknown MB (Box 1 (8-Weblogs), Folder 4)
    Geof Huth is a little-used weblog that includes occasional documentation of Geof Huth and drafts of poems in progress. The primary purpose of this blog is to guard against cybersquatting. URL: http://geofhuth.blogspot.com; Blog Files: Arranged in reverse chronological order. Consists of an archived copy of the weblog.; Paper Files: Arranged in chronological order by month and thereunder in reverse chronological order of blog posting. Consists of a printout the weblog.
  - One Million Footnotes, 2004-2006; 8.8; 0.25 cubic ft. + unknown MB
    A weblog that includes single numbered sentences published at a usual rate of one per day. The weblog's prospectus describes the blog as "Footnotes to a nonexistent book, a series of observations, a novel without the plot, the autobiography of an imagination, linked poetry of the everyday world, an impossible goal". URL: http://onemillionfootnotes.blogspot.com
    - One Million Footnotes, 2004 (Box 1 (8-Weblogs), Folder 5)
    - One Million Footnotes, 2005 (Box 1 (8-Weblogs), Folder 6)
    - One Million Footnotes, 2006 January-2006 October (Box 1 (8-Weblogs), Folder 7)
  - Subseries I: pdqb, 2003-2006; 1 folder + unknown MB
    A weblog that describes Geof Huth's pdqb publications, which document Huth's family and include some short-run editions of his artwork. Some entries are retrodated so the postings coincide with the original date of publication of the issues. The weblog's prospectus describes the blog as "A bibliography of the publications of pdqb, a micropress publishing documentation of the family GNET". URL: http://pdqb.blogspot.com; Blog Files: Arranged in reverse chronological order. Consists of an archived copy of the weblog.; Paper Files: Arranged in chronological order by month and thereunder in reverse chronological order of blog posting. Consists of a printout the weblog.
  - Subseries J: qbdp: the mailartworks, 2004-2006; unknown cubic feet + 554 MB